let CustomerServiceQuestions = [
    {
        "question": "What is the price difference to upgrade to a large size drink?",
        "option1": "$0.50",
        "option2": "$0.75",
        "option3": "$0.85",
        "option4": "$0.25",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Do we offer milk substitutes?",
        "option1": "We do offer almond milk sub for tea lattes.",
        "option2": "We don't. We only offer whole milk.",
        "option3": "We do offer soy milk sub for our lattes.",
        "option4": "We don't. We only offer 2% milk.",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What are our caffeine free drink options?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "All of our smoothies, breezes, creme brulee, water base fruit tea, taro milk tea, and horchata milk tea.",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 3
    },
      
    {
        "question": "Which of our toppings are vegan?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "Pearls, ",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 3
    }
];